{
  "24": {
    "answer_false1": "Launching an airstrike",
    "type": 2,
    "answer_false3": "Being approached by an enemy ship",
    "question": "Which of the following will not cause the Carrier detection gauge to fill up?",
    "answer_right": "Being affected by Flooding",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Being affected by Burn",
    "id": 24
  },
  "25": {
    "answer_false1": "High",
    "type": 2,
    "answer_false3": "Low",
    "question": "What must a stage's threat level be in order to use the Auto Search combat function?",
    "answer_right": "Safe",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Medium",
    "id": 25
  },
  "26": {
    "answer_false1": "70",
    "type": 2,
    "answer_false3": "100",
    "question": "What is the current ship level cap?",
    "answer_right": "120",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "90",
    "id": 26
  },
  "27": {
    "answer_false1": "4",
    "type": 2,
    "answer_false3": "15",
    "question": "What is the maximum number of commissions that can be carried out daily?",
    "answer_right": "No limit",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "8",
    "id": 27
  },
  "28": {
    "answer_false1": "Coins",
    "type": 2,
    "answer_false3": "Wisdom Cubes",
    "question": "Which of the following cannot be purchased with Gems?",
    "answer_right": "Ship EXP",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Oil",
    "id": 28
  },
  "15": {
    "answer_false1": "Sail downwind",
    "type": 1,
    "answer_false3": "Stay still",
    "question": "In order to minimize the take-off time of aircraft, carriers should do which of the following?",
    "answer_right": "Sail upwind",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Sail crosswind",
    "id": 15
  },
  "16": {
    "answer_false1": "Steam catapult",
    "type": 1,
    "answer_false3": "Hydraulic catapult",
    "question": "Which of the following was not a mechanism used by carriers or warships to launch planes?",
    "answer_right": "Mechanical spring",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Gunpowder catapult",
    "id": 16
  },
  "17": {
    "answer_false1": "Hypertension",
    "type": 1,
    "answer_false3": "Scurvy",
    "question": "Sailors ate barley rice to prevent which one of the following diseases?",
    "answer_right": "Beriberi",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Gangrene",
    "id": 17
  },
  "18": {
    "answer_false1": "Bulbous",
    "type": 1,
    "answer_false3": "Inverted",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a ship bow type?",
    "answer_right": "Armored",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Clipper",
    "id": 18
  },
  "19": {
    "answer_false1": "Impact fuze",
    "type": 1,
    "answer_false3": "Barometric fuze",
    "question": "The VT Fuze is also called which of the following?",
    "answer_right": "Proximity fuze",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Time fuze",
    "id": 19
  },
  "20": {
    "answer_false1": "Overpenetration",
    "type": 1,
    "answer_false3": "Armor-Piercing",
    "question": "What is it called when a shell damages a vessel by exploding in the nearby waters instead of scoring a direct hit?",
    "answer_right": "Near Miss",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "ASW shelling",
    "id": 20
  },
  "21": {
    "answer_false1": "High-angle guns",
    "type": 1,
    "answer_false3": "Ramming",
    "question": "Which of the following is an effective way to attack submarines?",
    "answer_right": "Depth charges",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Throwing potatoes",
    "id": 21
  },
  "22": {
    "answer_false1": "Normal shells",
    "type": 2,
    "answer_false3": "HE shells",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a naval gun ammunition type in the game?",
    "answer_right": "Flare shells",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "AP shells",
    "id": 22
  },
  "23": {
    "answer_false1": "Fighters",
    "type": 2,
    "answer_false3": "Torp Bombers",
    "question": "Which of the following is not factored into the Airspace Control calculation?",
    "answer_right": "ASW Aircraft",
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "answer_false2": "Dive Bombers",
    "id": 23
  },
  "all": [
    15,
    16,
    17,
    18,
    19,
    20,
    21,
    22,
    23,
    24,
    25,
    26,
    27,
    28
  ]
}